A Guide to the Japan Society records FA766
Rockefeller Archive Center
Japan Society records
1955-2017
Rockefeller Archive Center
Japan Society. (New York, N.Y.)
FA766
2.07 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, 1 document box and 2 half boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Records are arranged as received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to RAC by the Japan Society in 2012. Collection consists of two accessions transferred to RAC in 2013 and 2014 - 2013:033 and 2014:008.
Scope and Contents
Collection contains annual reports and select publications of the Japan Society.
Separated Materials
Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
- Japan Society records, Accession 2013:033, 1955-2012; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
  - The Quiet Builders; A Story of the Friendship of Two Men: A History of the Reconciliation of the Two Countries, 2013:033:001 (Item 2013:033:001)
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Publications, 1997, 2007, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Japan Society 90th Anniversary Annual Dinner, 1997 May 17; 2013:033:002 (Item 2013:033:002)
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Japan Society records, Accession 2014:008, 2008-2014; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter document box
  - Corporate Calendar, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Calendar of Events, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Celebrating a Century, 1907-2007 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Japan Society records, Accession 2015:103, 2015-2016; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Corporate Calendars (Box 3)
  - Annual Report, 2015-2016 (Box 3)
- Japan Society records, Accession 2017:111, 2016-2017; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter document box
  - Calendar of Events pamphlets, 2016-2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, September - October 2016 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, November - December 2016 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, January - February 2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, March - April 2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, May - June 2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, July - August 2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, September - October 2017 (Box 4)
  - Calendar of Events, November - December 2017 (Box 4)